
Line                                                                  
----                                                                  
ID: 2040030 NAME: Scroll for Helmet for DEX 30%                       
ID: 2040322 NAME: Scroll for Earring for LUK 30%                      
ID: 2040327 NAME: Scroll for Earring for HP 30%                       
ID: 2040426 NAME: Scroll for Topwear for LUK 30%                      
ID: 2040533 NAME: Scroll for Overall for STR 30%                      
ID: 2040626 NAME: Scroll for Bottomwear for DEX 30%                   
ID: 2040932 NAME: Scroll for Shield for STR 30%                       
ID: 2043018 NAME: Scroll for One-Handed Sword for Accuracy 30%        
ID: 2043113 NAME: Scroll for One-Handed Axe for Accuracy 30%          
ID: 2043213 NAME: Scroll for One-Handed BW for Accuracy 30%           
ID: 2044013 NAME: Scroll for Two-Handed Sword for Accuracy 30%        
ID: 2044113 NAME: Scroll for Two-Handed Axe for Accuracy 30%          
ID: 2044213 NAME: Scroll for Two-Handed BW for Accuracy 30%           
ID: 2044313 NAME: Scroll for Spear for Accuracy 30%                   
ID: 2044413 NAME: Scroll for Pole-Arm for Accuracy 30%                
ID: 2044804 NAME: Scroll for Knuckler for Attack 30%                  
ID: 2044808 NAME: Scroll for Knuckle for Accuracy 30%                 
ID: 2044904 NAME: Scroll for Gun for Attack 30%                       
ID: 2040728 NAME: Balrog's STR Scroll 30%                             
ID: 2040729 NAME: Balrog's INT Scroll 30%                             
ID: 2040730 NAME: Balrog's LUK Scroll 30%                             
ID: 2040731 NAME: Balrog's DEX Scroll 30%                             
ID: 2040732 NAME: Balrog's HP Scroll 30%                              
ID: 2040733 NAME: Balrog's MP Scroll 30%                              
ID: 2040734 NAME: Balrog's Speed Scroll 30%                           
ID: 2040735 NAME: Balrog's Jump Scroll 30%                            
ID: 2040736 NAME: Balrog's Accuracy Scroll 30%                        
ID: 2040737 NAME: Balrog's Avoidability Scroll 30%                    
ID: 2040738 NAME: Balrog's Defense Scroll 30%                         
ID: 2041113 NAME: Dark Scroll for Rings for STR 30%                   
ID: 2041115 NAME: Dark Scroll for Rings for INT 30%                   
ID: 2041117 NAME: Dark Scroll for Rings for DEX 30%                   
ID: 2041119 NAME: Dark Scroll for Rings for LUK 30%                   
ID: 2041313 NAME: Dark Scroll for Belts for STR 30%                   
ID: 2041315 NAME: Dark Scroll for Belts for INT 30%                   
ID: 2041317 NAME: Dark Scroll for Belts for DEX 30%                   
ID: 2041319 NAME: Dark Scroll for Belts for LUK 30%                   
ID: 2049106 NAME: [6th Anniversary] Dark Scroll for Gloves for ATT 30%
ID: 2049201 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for STR 30%               
ID: 2049203 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for DEX 30%               
ID: 2049205 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for INT 30%               
ID: 2049207 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for LUK 30%               
ID: 2049209 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for HP 30%                
ID: 2049211 NAME: Dark Scroll for Accessory for MP 30%                


